Hello everyone! The Equal Love.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Kanji characters now.
Hello everyone! Equal Love's
Kanji now.
Look, it's written like this.
Because then it would look like...
Hello everyone! Of equal love...
Hello everyone!
Oh, sorry, sorry, sorry.
That's how we do it.
Hello everyone! I'm Yui Noguchi from Equal Love.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know. I'm Yui Noguchi from Equal Love!
All right, all right.
Hello everyone! I'm Yori Noguchi from Equal Love, Hitomi Takamatsu.
I'm Sana Onohashi.
Hello!
Today, we're here...
The Odaiba Dinosaur Expo is being held in Odaiba.
The Odaiba Dinosaur Expo.
They're coming from Fukui on the bullet train.
Yay!
When you're here, it's like you're a big dinosaur.
It's like being eaten by dinosaurs here, Kiaro.
What's that? Kiaro?
Kiaro?
Yes, Kiaro is an hour late again today.
He overslept.
Kiaro, you really got eaten, didn't you? Kira, you're going to be an hour late again today.
Kira-chan really got eaten, didn't she?
Maybe she's in there, too.
She might be inside.
She might be in there.
We have to find her.
So, this is our 16th single.
Norotte Norotte is the tie-up song for the Odaiba Kowloon Expo 2024.
It's flowing.
It's playing.
We're having fun.
I'd like you to try it.
There seem to be lots of different areas.
Let's go to the goods area first.
Kiaga hasn't arrived yet.
I'd like to go there with everyone.
Here we go!
This is it.
What do you want?
It's cute.
What's this for? Look at these... they're like the biggest bones I've ever seen... and I wonder if any of them are here.
I don't see any.
What's wrong with it? It's so cute, I love it. It's holding a stuffed animal.
Maybe I'll get a red one.
It's good. It's good.
I'll go with red.
That's it!
Yay!
They sell all kinds of stuff.
There are so many kinds.
What?
You're kidding?
Thank you very much.
That's a CD shop.
Thank you kindly.
Thank you very much.
It's him.
Great. So you want something with Kya-chan in it?
Oh, sure, because no one else might have hair.
As a hair camouflage.
What do you mean, I always do my hair like this?
You're so cool, though, you're so in character.
I certainly can't imagine it.
It stands out.
I think it's cute, the blue with the pink hair.
It's a bit American, that's for sure.
Well, let's give it to Chara.
Let's go to venue one.
There's a first, second and third floor.
This place is huge!
What's there to see? Let's go.
Aaah!
Oh, wait!
Is it big?
It's huge!
Oh, my God!
There they are! They're here! - They're, er... - They're big! The dinosaurs are making so much noise! They're calling us... because I'm big.
I'm sure you're right.
How big?
Who's big?
Who's a dinosaur?
Dinosaur.
It's huge!
He's huge!
His face is tiny.
You scared me!
Whoa!
Now!
That's a bit scary!
You're scary! You're scaring me! A bit scary! I'm a bit scared! Are you looking at me? Are you looking at me? I'm a bit scared, a bit scared, a bit scared.
I'm a bit scared.
Maybe a bit scary.
It's Kija!
It's Kya!
She's angry.
I'm scared.
Close, close, close.
That's a lot of stuff, but it's more than enough for one minute. - I'll give you this.
I hope you're not doing your hair or anything.
LOL!
It's cute, though.
She's cute, though.
America.
Kia, please don't cry.
We're going.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Sora. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Sora, head to venue two.
That's where the pairs were supposed to be.
Oh, good, good.
So, with the Manatsu Kihara pair, me and Hitomi pair.
We'd like to head to venue 2.
Great.
It seems that here, dinosaur research from the beginning to the world, Japanese dinosaur research, and even Fukui's dinosaur research is being introduced!
Research.
It's a research hall.
Hmm.
So...
Let's go have a look.
Yeah, okay.
It's amazing.
Queen Saurus Petriasis.
Oh, my God.
Herbivorous dinosaurs.
Hey.
I wonder what happened to it.
Great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great MEME
me
Me.
me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me me.
I love Raptors.
I love Raptors. They have these amazing fangs.
How many fangs do you have?
I mean, Kiara's only on like three newspapers, right?
Three papers and that's it?
That's what I'm talking about.
You mean they found a lot of fossils from Japan?
There are a lot of other fossils, seats, they've been found.
Why Fukui?
Fukui was the strongest, but it had a big boss, so everyone survived to the end.
So they all survived to the end and were saved.
So, Dr. Snow is a common name? Students were showing up.
Dr. Sekieiya and Iori.
Dr. Shibata's here, too.
Dr. Kawabe is here, too.
Want a comp?
Next, point me in the direction of...
This is the Dinosaur Society.
I'm Dr. Sybert.
Dr. Sybert, tell me.
Who is it?
I'm Dr. Qawwab.
He's got a cute face.
I'm sorry, you're introducing the dinosaurs.
I'm sorry, I introduced you to Dr. Qawwab.
Look, the baby's moving.
That's amazing.
That's a lot of babies born at once.
You look like a mother.
It's like duck bridge.
Yes, but it's like a duck bridge.
But it's like this, it's a duck bridge, meaty, meaty...
Flesh on the child.
That's great.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha...
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha. - Well, I'm sure you're used to it.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
There's a bullet train.
This time, we all want to start this bullet train with everything we've got.
We'll start this bullet train together, mixed up with the simics.
But I'm a little concerned.
Noro Noro is on it, too.
Noro Noro is in it too.
I'm going to be like...
It's fun music.
All right, then.
I've got to make sure I don't fall off.
Enjoy your trip, Mr. T.
We're leaving!
I'm so happy! She's definitely coming back to Flor!
I want to run!
What? It's true!
You're beautiful! That's amazing! I don't have a ME.
Me.
It's a nice trip, much slower.
You can look at the pages slowly, surely, surely, but only surely...
It's just in front of the headquarters.
Don't get too excited.
How big is it? How big is it?
I can't see his face yet.
It's even bigger than I thought it would be.
Wait a minute.
Come on, let's go.
Oh, scary!
It's so thin!
Wait a minute!
Your eyes are so beautiful.
It's a little bit amazing.
The moment I got to the middle, I got a little pissed off.
Boo-boo-boo!
Boo-boo-boo.
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry.
So, I had a lot of fun at the Odaiba Dinosaur Expo,
From here, you see, on the first floor, there is also a gourmet restaurant from Fukui Prefecture,
I'm so happy!!!
You must have been hungry.
It's starting to look like eels!
Let's eat together.
Let's go eat.
So we went to the food area.
There's so much food.
Can we choose anything?
Anything?
What's good?
What do you want?
What? I was just wondering.
Sauce katsudon, oroshi soba, croquettes...
Petit katsu and...
Enbata-don.
Enbutter donburi.
So here's the rice we chose.
Looks delicious!
All of it.
I'll have it all.
It's all on the menu, isn't it?
Well, you've got it, then, ladies and gentlemen.
Bon appétit.
What?
That's a lot of weight.
That's great.
It's so crispy.
Maybe there's corn in it.
Yeah, it's good.
That's good.
I'm so happy.
Is it good?
I've always wanted to eat something like this.
Good girl.
I'm happy for you.
It was an exhibition about how you came on the bullet train from Fukui.
How was it? Fun for adults and children alike.
I saw the Petch Wrap, and it was even better than I thought it would be this month.
I said it was really strong, and I remember it well, and there were some historical relics and stuff.
I'm happy with what I saw.
Yes, I was making a rider.
Me.
I'll be happy if it's a lot of boo-boos, boo-boos, boo-boos, boo-boos, boo-boos, boo-boos, boo-boos, boo-boos, boo-boos, boo-boos, boo-boos, boo-boos...
Amen something up while I'm getting on, but I'm a bit hungry, so I'd like to eat well with everyone. Bon appétit.
So, the Odaiba Dinosaur Expo will be open until 6 May.
So please come and visit us.
Does this mean you're doing winks too?
Oh! That's right!
You should come!
Come on!